getfave.com 2008-02-12

# Fave Privacy

Privacy

Fave Media Inc. recognizes its obligation to its users, customers, and online visitors to adhere to the highest standards of decency, fairness, and integrity in all its operations. Likewise, Fave is dedicated to protecting and enhancing consumer privacy on the internet.

#### Gathering and Use of Information

Fave collects personal information from our users only on a voluntary basis. However, in order to create an account with Fave, you must provide your zip code and a valid email address. Personal information received from any user will be used only for internal purposes.

Fave contracts with third-party service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions. Suppliers and service providers are required to keep confidential the information received on behalf of Fave and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us. Fave will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by law enforcement action, subpoena, or local law. Fave may need to disclose its aggregate customer information to financial institutions in order to secure financing. Fave could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or some or all of its assets could be acquired. If such a combination or acquisition occurs, your personal information will necessarily be a business asset that is acquired in the transaction.

#### Security

Fave collects your zip code and email address at registration. Occasionally, we may also ask for personal information for our own internal marketing use. You may provide this information on a voluntary basis. To help prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Fave has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

#### Email

In registering, you agree to receive membership-related email. This will include emails confirming your registration, notifying you of membership policy changes, and newsletters of upcoming events. You should ensure that your email address is always up to date so that you receive all critical notices of membership policy changes.

#### Links

The Fave software and website contains links to other sites. Our intent is to link to websites that share our high standards of decency, fairness, and integrity. We try our best to ensure that these links are safe for children, but the privacy and data collection practices on any linked websites are entirely separate from Fave and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Fave shall not be responsible for any failure on the part of any linked websites to comply with any privacy policy posted on the website, or any contractual or other legal obligations to which the operators of such website may be subject. In addition, other websites, which may contain material not suitable for children, may also link to the Fave website without Fave's knowledge or consent. Fave has no responsibility for the content, policies or actions of these websites.

#### Changes and Updates to the Privacy Policy

Fave's content and features may be updated, revised, modified and supplemented. Fave reserves the right to change the information, features, products, policies, promotions, disclosures and disclaimers at any time. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our website. Please check the policy periodically for changes. At the end of the policy we indicate the date of an update to the Privacy Policy. It is your obligation to review the website periodically to review those changes.

#### Summary

As in our other business operations, Fave approaches our communications on the internet with respect for, and commitment to, individual privacy rights, concern, and respect for our children. We support active self-regulation of this new environment to ensure that responsible marketers can maintain the right to use all communication media to interact with consumers.

#### Questions

If you have any questions about Fave's online privacy policies or procedures, or if you would like to remove your personal information from our database, please contact us by emailing to [support@getfave.com](mailto:support@getfave.com).

Fave Media Inc.'s headquarters are located at:

**2350 N Clark St.  
Chicago, IL 60614-3423  
**

This Privacy Policy has been updated as of September 25, 2007.
